{
  "questions":
  [
    {
      "question": "I'll make him an offer ___ ",
      "answers": [
        "too good to be true",
        "he can't refuse",
        "better than this",
        "that stinks"
      ],
      "answerindex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Are you crying? There's no crying in ___ !",
      "answers": [
        "Neverland",
        "Disneyland",
        "Baseball",
        "Boxing"
      ],
      "answerindex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Woody to Buzz: 'You are a ___ !",
      "answers": [
        "Maggot",
        "Space ranger",
        "Toy",
        "Real one"
      ],
      "answerindex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "He says on the bow of the Titanic: 'I'm the king of the world!'",
      "answers": [
        "Jack Bauer",
        "Jack Dawson",
        "Da Vinci",
        "Rose Bukater"
      ],
      "answerindex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "This title character: 'I am friend of Sarah Connor. Can I see her please?",
      "answers": [
        "Running Man",
        "The Terminator",
        "Superman",
        "Batman"
      ],
      "answerindex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Joe Pesci in this film: 'I'm funny how, I mean funny like I'm a clown?'",
      "answers": [
        "Home Alone",
        "The Godfather",
        "Goodfellas",
        "Lethal Weapon"
      ],
      "answerindex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "This title character wants to 'phone home'",
      "answers": [
        "Nemo",
        "Gilbert Grape",
        "E.T",
        "Stitch"
      ],
      "answerindex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "From this film: 'You're gonna need a bigger boat'",
      "answers": [
        "Titanic",
        "Free Willy",
        "Around the world in 80 days",
        "Jaws"
      ],
      "answerindex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Him, hanging from a cliff: 'Brother, help me!'",
      "answers": [
        "Sasuke",
        "Mufasa",
        "Thor",
        "Aladdin"
      ],
      "answerindex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "You'll get your rent when you ___ !",
      "answers": [
        "die",
        "fix this damn door",
        "eat lead",
        "ask nicely"
      ],
      "answerindex": 1
    }
  ]
}